Guide to the Stanford University, Symbolic Systems Program, Honors Theses SC4-6534
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Symbolic Systems Program, honors theses
1993-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Symbolic Systems Program
SC4-6534
1.25 Linear Feet (19 volumes in 3 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Symbolic Systems Program.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Symbolic Systems Program.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Student papers.; Stanford University. Symbolic Systems Program
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Mercer, Noah, ="simple" render="italic">Computers and the self: approaches to agent design., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Pauly, Marc, ="simple" render="italic">Gödelian formalities - details of Gödel's second incompleteness theorem., 1996 (Box 1)
  - Perfors, Amy, ="simple" render="italic">Slow and steady doesn't win the race: the relation of infant information processing skills to later linguistic performance., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Schapiro, Anna C., ="simple" render="italic">A connectionist model of a continuous developmental transition in the balance scale task., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Soergel, David, ="simple" render="italic">OrganISM: an abstract representation paradigm for intelligent information networks., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Wobbrock, Jacob Otto, ="simple" render="italic">The law and policy of autonomous software agents., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Norman, Kenneth Andrew, ="simple" render="italic">Is consciousness the gatekeeper of memory?., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Flannery, Matthew and David Merrill, ="simple" render="italic">Faces and voices: social and cognitive effects of new interface paradigms., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Skolnick, Deena, ="simple" render="italic">Interactions between mutual exclusivity and lexical contrast in word learning., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Lindsay, Jon R., ="simple" render="italic">A biological basis for being-in-the-world: autopoiesis and Heideggerian phenomenology., 1995 (Box 1)
  - Barkis, William B, ="simple" render="italic">A new insight into a fundamental neural mechanism of learning, memory, and neuron death: understanding the regulation of NMDA receptor expression., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Tauber, Ellen R., ="simple" render="italic">The conceptimator: an expert system for conceptual cost estimating of building foundations., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chiao, Joan, ="simple" render="italic">"Do they all look alike?": an fMRI study on expertise for same- versus other-race faces., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Soergel, David, ="simple" render="italic">OrganISM, an abstract representation paradigm for intelligent information networks., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Mayer, Marissa A., ="simple" render="italic">A natural language interface for the advisable planner., 1997 (Box 2)
  - Meganathan, Indirajith, ="simple" render="italic">Art therapy: complexity, expressiveness, and artistic style., 1996 (Box 2)
  - Srinivasan, Mahesh, ="simple" render="italic">Nominal classification and conceptual organization: a cross-linguistic perspective from English to Mandarin Chinese., 2005 (Box 2)
  - Henry, Kevin Christopher, ="simple" render="italic">Combining conventional search techniques with machine learning in the game of Go., no date (Box 2)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Kao, Justine T., "A computational analysis of poetic craft in contemporary professional and amateur poetry", 2011 May (Box 1)